<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wilhelmina&#39;s Art Gallery</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wilhelmina&#39;s Art Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 14:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Robert Bodem</title>
      <link>/artists/robert-bodem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/robert-bodem/</guid>
      <description>Bodem graduated cum laude from Boston University with a undergraduate degree in Sculpture (1995) and Master of Fine Arts (1998). Upon graduation, Bodem was awarded the prestigious Alert S. and Ester B. Kahn Award for his talent in figurative sculpture. This facilitated Bodem’s move to Florence, Italy where he founded the Florence Academy of Art’s sculpture program. Under his directorship, this rose to become one of the world’s premier programs to study naturalistic figurative sculpture and Bodem is recognised for nurturing a generation of highly prolific sculptors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wilhelmina von Blumenthal</title>
      <link>/wilhelmina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wilhelmina/</guid>
      <description>In 2022 she led the coordination and installation of 23 monumental sculptures for the exhibition Nothing is Permanent in the city of Esch-sur-Alzette, last year’s European Capital of Culture. Amongst them were works by Tony Cragg, Wim Delvoye, Katinka Bock, Tina Gillen, Hisae Ikenaga, Barthélémy Toguo, Bertrand, Ney, Wang Du, Guillaume Bijl, Bernard Venet and Erwin Wurm.
She was also the driving force behind Barthélémy Toguo’s retrospective exhibition Faith Can Move Mountains at the Villa Merkel in Esslingen which brought together hundreds of watercolours, paintings, ceramics, installations and enamels from 1995 to the present day, including works that were created especially for the exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wilhelmina&#39;s Art Gallery</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Les expositions du peintre Silvère Jarrosson sont des jalons de son cheminement artistique, chacune abordant une thématique, un regard sur la peinture contemporaine et la façon de l&amp;rsquo;exposer. Solo ou collectives, en galerie ou dans des institutions culturelles, chacune traduit une certaine lecture de son œuvre.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
